Well, this is your end times news update
and as you can see right here, the UAE
welcomed a bad dawn. A nice little hair
dance. Looks like I need to have a talk
with my wife and ask her why she does
not do this for me whenever I walk
through the door. On second thought, I'm
not sure if the chronic neck pain would
be worth the ego boost. Now, speaking of
ego, we have Mr. Ego himself to visit
Abrahamic family house in Abu Dhabi,
where he will be the first president to
tour the complex. And for those who do
not know, the Abrahamic family house is
a
interfaith complex in Abu Dhabi. And
this interfaith complex houses a mosque,
a church, and a synagogue. Now, get
this, the undertaking was inspired by
the document on human paternity signed
by Pope Francis on behalf of the
Catholic Church and also signed by Ahmed
El Tahib on behalf of the Al Azure
mosque. The project is an initiative
towards the end times one world
religion. I mean I'm sorry tolerance and
coexistence among Abrahamic faiths. I'm
sorry I'm dyslexic. Now it houses the
St. Francis Church, the Imam Al Tahib
mosque and the Moses
Benon Synagogue in separate structures.
Here's a picture right here of the
facility. And as we can see the purpose
of the Abrahamic family house aims to
serve as a community for
interreligious dialogue and exchange and
be a physical manifestation of the
document on human fraternity. Now the
complex seeks to represent interfaith
coexistence preserves the unique
character of the religions represented
in build bridges between human
civilization and the Abrahamic messages.
Please tell me you can see what's going
on here. The same guy who was on a
Middle East tour to bring peace and to
bring forth the Abraham Accords is also
going to be the first president to tour
the Abrahamic family house which is all
about the interfaith or interreligious
agenda. You can't make this up. Now in
other news, we have the UAE and the US
agreeing to establish the US UAE AI
acceleration partnership. That just
sounds so wonderful where we can see the
UAE is set to deepen AI links with the
United States. Now, Nvidia scores big
with a bad dawn brokering a major AI
export pack with the UAE and US tech
giants, which makes sense since the UAE
is all on board with AI governance. As
we can actually see the Microsoft
president wants to see the US replicate
Abu Dhabi's AI efforts where he is
quoted saying to the US Senate Commerce
how we need to bring it to America. What
he's talking about is Abu Dhabi's AI
governance called TAM. And TAM is a
state-of-the-art unified digital
ecosystem of over 900 government and
private sector services. The word TAM
translates to consider it done in
Arabic. I've tried to warn you guys,
they are literally treating AI like a
genie. Now, it represents a guiding
light to offering superior customer
service. At TAM, we are focused on
continually developing and providing the
best experience for each valued user.
TAM prides itself on accessibility and
allowing people within Abu Dhabi to
access everyday vital services across
health care, housing, citizenship,
residency, and much much more. But we
can go back to this article right here
about the Microsoft president talking
about how we need to have apps that
simplify the process of renewing driver
license, reporting potholes, obtaining
various forms, and other services. He
says, "You can do all these things with
your phone, by the way, and you can do
this today in Abu Dhabi." Now, at one
point, he was shown Abu Dhabi's TAM,
government service AI assistant, which
acts as a onestop shop for all
government services. And as we can see
right here, Microsoft has been a
proponent of the UAE's AI aspirations in
recent years. The company made a $ 1.5
billion investment in the UAE AI and
cloud company G42 in 2024 and later
announced that it would open its
researchbased AI for good lab in Abu
Dhabi. Oh, thank the good Lord that they
named it AI for good lab. I mean, we
really missed a bullet there. As we can
see, the UAE is not alone in the Middle
East for their desire of AI governance
as Saudi Arabia launches AI venture
Humane. As we can see, AWS and Humane
announce a more than $5 billion
investment to accelerate AI adoption in
Saudi Arabia and globally. And as we
see, Humane and Nvidia announced
strategic partnership to build AI
factories of the future in Saudi Arabia.
Isn't that lovely? Since we're talking
about AI in the Middle East, we have
this right here. How Mr. A Bad Dawn
suggests US takeover of Gaza to make it
a freedom zone. Yeah, I'm not sure about
you guys, but this right here is giving
me 1984 vibes. War is peace. Freedom is
slavery. Ignorance is strength. And AI
surveillance is a freedom zone. You will
obey. With all this AI in the news, I
need to bring this back up to your
attention. speak on it once again
because nobody else is talking about
this. How the House budget bill would
put a 10year pause on state AI
regulation. As we can see, the big
beautiful bill before the House Energy
and Commerce Committee under the budget
reconciliation process would prevent
states from enforcing any law or
regulation for AI models. where
apparently it says in this big beautiful
bill, "No state or political subdivision
thereof may enforce any law or
regulation regulating artificial
intelligence models, artificial
intelligence systems, or automated
decision systems during the 10-year
period." Apparently, this ban would
allow AI companies to ignore consumer
privacy protections, let deep fakes
spread, and allow companies to profile
and deceive consumers using AI. Yeah,
this sounds like a wonderful idea. What
could go wrong? That wraps it up for
your End Times news update. Things are
accelerating at such a rapid rate. It is
so hard to keep up with it. My goodness,
the writing is on the wall clearly of
the times that we are living in. So
therefore, we continue to focus on the
Lord. And just remember, what really
matters is your personal relationship
with the Lord and your relationship with
others. Growing in maturity, having your
mind renewed and transformed daily
through his word, walking forth, living
by faith and not by sight, working on
your own emotions and situations that
the Lord places you in. Do not allow the
news in this world to cause stress,
fear, anxiety. The Lord does not give us
the spirit of fear, but the spirit of
power, love, and a sound mind, and peace
that surpasses all understanding that
will guard your heart and your mind.
Philippians 4:6 and uh through 8. So, I
just want you guys to remember that.
Keep your eyes on the Lord. Everything
going on right now, it's good to, you
know, have your finger on the pulse, but
at the same time, if it's causing you
stress and anxiety, just don't look at
it, you know. And if these videos cause
stress, stop watching them, okay? I
don't want them to cause stress. That's
why I try to bring sarcasm. I try to,
you know, bring some type of humor
because honestly guys, comedy is the
greatest remedy against tragedy. And
what's going on in the world is
completely tragic. People are going
their own way trying to build a god in
their own image with artificial
intelligence. And people are rebelling
against God. People are deceived at such
a high level. It's so disheartening. But
we got to be able to laugh here. We got
to have some type of joy, right? With
some, you know, jokes. Hope I can, you
know, bring that to you guys. But with
that all being said, just focus on the
Lord. Stay true to him in your own
personal walk. And the way you do that
is by just talking to him. Go to him. He
wants to hear you talk to him. Pray to
him and go forth, guys. I love you all
so much. Right. God bless. Remember, the
just shall live by faith.